<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Exercise - Class 01</string>
    <string name="textCenter" translatable="false">Alan Turing</string>
    <string name="textCenter2" translatable="false">Ada Lovelace</string>
    <string name="historyLabel">A historia do Alan</string>
    <string name="historyLabel2">The Ada Lovelace Story</string>
    <string name="imageDescription">Alan Turing\'s image</string>
    <string name="imageDescription2">Image of Ada Lovelace</string>
    <string name="personDescription"><![CDATA[Alan Mathison Turing (June 23, 1912 – June 7, 1954) was a British mathematician,[1] computer scientist, logician, cryptanalyst, philosopher, and theoretical biologist. Turing was highly influential in the development of modern theoretical computer science, providing a formalization of the concepts of algorithm and computation with the Turing machine, which can be considered a model of a general-purpose computer.[2][3][4] He is widely considered the father of theoretical computer science and artificial intelligence.[5] Despite these accomplishments he was never fully recognized in his home country during his lifetime for being homosexual and because much of his work was covered by the Official Secrets Act. During World War II Turing worked for the Government Code and Cipher School (GC&CS) at Bletchley Park, the British cryptanalysis center that produced ultra intelligence. For a time he led Hut 8, the section responsible for German naval cryptanalysis. There he developed various techniques to speed up the breaking of German ciphers, including improvements to the pre-war Polish bombing method, as well as an electromechanical machine that could find settings for the Enigma machine. Turing played a crucial role in breaking intercepted coded messages that enabled the Allies to defeat the Nazis in many crucial engagements, including the Battle of the Atlantic, and in doing so helped them win the war. Due to the problems of counterfactual history, it is difficult to estimate the precise effect that ultra-intelligence had on the war[6] but it has been estimated that this work shortened the war in Europe by more than two years and saved more than 14 million lives.[7] ]]]></string>
    <string name="personDescription2">Augusta Ada Byron King, Countess of Lovelace (née Byron, 10 December 1815 – 27 November 1852), now known as Ada Lovelace, was an English mathematician and writer. She is now recognized primarily for having written the first algorithm to be processed by a machine, Charles Babbage\'s Analytical Engine.[1][2] During the time she was involved with Babbage\'s project, she developed the algorithms that would allow the machine to compute the values ​​of mathematical functions, as well as publishing a collection of notes on the analytical engine. For this work she is considered the first programmer in all of history [3] [4]. Lovelace was born on 10 December 1815 and is the only legitimate child of the poet Lord Byron and his wife Anne Isabella Anabella Byron,[5] Lady Wentworth. All of Lord Byron\'s other children were born out of wedlock.[6] Byron was the writer of one of the versions of Don Juan.[7] He separated from his wife a month after Ada was born and left England for good four months later. He ended up dying of illness during the Greek War of Independence when Ada was eight years old. Ada\'s mother fostered Ada\'s interest in mathematics and logic in an effort to stop her from developing what she saw as Lord Byron\'s insanity. But Ada remained interested in her father and, at her request, she was buried beside him when he died.[8]</string>
</resources>